(Leonard:)You just listen to what she says...
(Leonard:)...and then you say something appropriate
in response.
(Sheldon:)To what end?
- Hi. Again.
- Hi.
(Sheldon:)- Hi.
(Leonard:)Anyway...
(Leonard:)...we brought home Indian food...
...and I know that
moving can be stressful...
(Leonard:)...and I find
that when I'm undergoing stress...
(Leonard:)...that good food
and company can have a comforting effect.
Also, curry's a natural laxative and
I don't have to tell you that, you know...
(Leonard:)...a clean colon is just one less thing
to worry about.
I'm no expert,
but in the context of a lunch invitation...
...you might wanna skip the reference
to bowel movements.
(Penny:)Oh, you're inviting me over to eat?
(Leonard:)Yes.
(Penny:)Oh, that's so nice. I'd love to.
(Leonard:)Great.
(Penny:)So, what do you guys do for fun
around here?
(Sheldon:)Well, today we tried masturbating
for money.